Guide to the Baldwin Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Baldwin family papers
1584-1977
MS 55
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
110.02
(214 boxes)
The papers detail the personal lives and professional careers of several generations and family lines of the Baldwin family. The legal, political, and business activities of family members in Connecticut, New York, and elsewhere are documented. Major topics include: family, women, law, education, Connecticut and New York politics and government, New Haven, Connecticut, and Yale University.
Baldwin family
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of members of the family, 1927-1959.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Existence and Location of Copies
Diaries (Boxes 83-84) of Simeon Eben Baldwin also available on microfilm (1,741 frames on 2 reels, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM72.
Papers of Roger Sherman Baldwin relating to the Amistad case also available on microfilm (275 frames on 1 reel, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM2.
Arrangement
Arranged in thirteen series: I. General Correspondence, 1595-1947. II. Ebenezer Baldwin, 1745-1776. III. Ebenezer Baldwin, 1790-1837. IV. Simeon Baldwin, 1761-1851. V. Roger Sherman Baldwin, 1826-1856. VI. Simeon Eben Baldwin, 1840-1927. VII. Roger Sherman Baldwin, 1793-1863. VIII. Henry De Forest Baldwin, 1862-1947. IX. William Hillhouse. X. Susan Winchester Baldwin. XI. Roger Sherman Baldwin, 1869-1956. XII. Other Family Members. XIII. Photographs; and two additions.
Scope and Contents
The papers detail the personal lives and professional careers of several generations and family lines of the Baldwin family. The legal, political, and business activities of family members in Connecticut, New York, and elsewhere are documented. Major topics include: family, women, law, education, Connecticut and New York politics and government, New Haven, Connecticut, and Yale University.
Series I, General Correspondence, 1595-1947, contains letters, enclosures, and related documents for several members and generations of the Baldwin family. A small portion of the earliest materials are typescripts, transcripts, or photocopies of original documents. Correspondence may also be arranged in Series II-XII, in the form of letters, letterbooks, or letterpress copybooks. Series I contains the personal and professional correspondence of such family members as: Ebenezer (1745-1776), Ebenezer (1790-1837), Simeon (1761-1851), Roger Sherman (1793-1863), Henry De Forest (1862-1947), Susan Winchester, and Roger Sherman Baldwin (1869-1956). Other family members, their friends and colleagues, and individuals are also represented in this series. Many family members exchanged letters through the years, thus the materials provide a view of life within the Baldwin family in addition to detailing the business, religious, commercial, and political activities of family members. A select list of correspondents found in Series I is provided in an Appendix.
Series II, Ebenezer Baldwin (1745-1776) contains the personal papers of this Yale graduate, tutor, and minister. A diary from the years 1763-1764, student notebooks, and almost two hundred (200) sermons are arranged in the series.
Series III, Ebenezer Baldwin (1790-1837) contains a student notebook (1807-1808) from Yale University in addition to orations and writings.
Series IV, Simeon Baldwin (1761-1851) contains account books and financial material, legal papers, printed material, student papers, and miscellanea documenting Baldwin's student years at Yale University, his legal career in Connecticut, and his political activities in New Haven and the state.
Series V, Roger Sherman Baldwin (1826-1856) contains a diary (1842), student notebooks, and other personal papers of Baldwin, who was the son of another Roger Sherman Baldwin (1793-1863).
SERIES VI, SIMEON EBEN BALDWIN (1840-1927) contains the account books, clippings, diaries, letterbooks, notes, speeches, student papers, topical files (including lecture notes), writings, briefs, lectures, printed material, and other papers documenting the personal life and professional career of Simeon Eben Baldwin, the prominent lawyer, educator, judge, and political figure. Account books include volumes relating to the Morning News, a late nineteenth century New Haven newspaper. Diaries includes nine handwritten volumes (boxes 83-84), 1851-1924, which are also available on microfilm (HM 72, 2 reels).
Clippings include items relating to Baldwin's political and judicial careers. A series of speeches on legal, political, and historical topics is arranged in boxes 90-94. Student papers files include material relating to the Clio Society (box 95, folders 989-990), a student organization which Baldwin served as an officer. Topical files contains material on many organizations and associations in addition to topics which interested Baldwin. A section of lecture notes contains the academic lessons Baldwin prepared for his law classes. Topics include: adoption, divorce, contracts, corporate law, insurance, marriage, railroads, and the constitution.
Files relating to Baldwin's publicized controversy with President Theodore Roosevelt are found in box 109. Briefs on many of Baldwin's legal cases from 1865-1893 are arranged in boxes 113-114.
Series VII, Roger Sherman Baldwin, 1793-1863, contains the account books, daybooks, legal papers, briefs, printed material, student papers, and other items documenting the life of Roger Sherman Baldwin, the noted Connecticut lawyer, governor, and senator. Account books date from 1796-1860, while legal papers and briefs (boxes 134-144) date from 1812-1862, and include information on many of the important legal cases Baldwin handled during his career.
Series VIII, Henry De Forest Baldwin, 1862-1947, contains the appointment books, letterpress copy books, speeches, topical files, and other papers of this New York City lawyer and municipal official. Appointment books and letterpress copybooks (boxes 148-171) detail the legal and political activities of Baldwin, who was an active reform figure in New York City politics. Letterpress copybooks are complete volumes from 1890-1944. Speeches and Topical Files material further detail the political attitudes and activities of Baldwin.
Series IX, William Hillhouse, 1757-1833, contains correspondence and papers relating to the estate of William Hillhouse.
Series X, Susan Winchester Baldwin, contains a notebook, written during her youth, and a group of letters which she wrote to her future husband from 1865-1897.
Series XI, Roger Sherman Baldwin, contains correspondence relating to Baldwin's service as an official at Fairfield (CT.) State Hospital.
Series XII, Other Family Members and Miscellenea, 1773-1915, contains correspondence, notebooks, account books, religious papers, and related material of several Baldwin family members. Individuals represented in this series include: Thomas Atwater, Edward Law Baldwin, Burr family members, Thomas Day, and Ellen M. Gifford.
Records for the Hartford and New Haven Turnpike and the Derby Fishing Company are also organized in this series.
Series XIII, Photographs, contains a collection of albums and loose photographs including pictures of many Baldwin family members including children, women, and men.
Biographical / Historical
Ebenezer Baldwin (1745-1776)
Ebenezer Baldwin (1745-1776) graduated from Yale University in 1763, served as a tutor from 1767-1770, and held the position of minister in the First Congregational Church in Danbury, Connecticut from 1770-1776. He served as a volunteer chaplain for the Danbury militia, a group which participated in the defense of New York City during the American Revolution. He contracted a fever at that time, and died in 1776.
Simeon Baldwin (1761-1851)
Simeon Baldwin (1761-1851) graduated from Yale University in 1781, he served as a tutor from 1783-1786, and began his New Haven law practice in 1787. He served as City Clerk (1789-1800), Clerk of the District and Circuit Courts of the United States for the District of Connecticut (1790-1803), United States Congressman (1803-1805), Clerk of the District Courts (re-appointment) (1805-1806), Associate Judge of the Superior Court (1806-1817), Commissioner of the Farmington Canal (1820-1830), and Mayor of New Haven (1826).
Roger Sherman Baldwin (1793-1863)
Roger Sherman Baldwin (1793-1863) graduated from Yale University in 1811, and began his law practice in New Haven in 1814. He served in New Haven and Connecticut politics (1826-1838), established a national reputation for his anti-slavery defense of slaves in the "Amistad" case (1839-1840), was elected governor of Connecticut (1844-1845), accepted the appointment and subsequent election to the U.S. Senate (1847-1851), and served as a delegate to the National Peace Convention (1861).
Simeon Eben Baldwin (1840-1927)
Simeon Eben Baldwin (1840-1927) graduated from Yale University in 1861, became a member of the bar in 1863, and was founder of the American Bar Association in 1878 and its president in 1890. He served as the Association's Director of the Bureau of Comparative Law (1907-1919), as an Associate Justice and Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of Connecticut, as the state's governor (1910-1914), and produced numerous articles and books.
Henry De Forest Baldwin (1862-1947)
Henry De Forest Baldwin (1862-1947) graduated from Yale University in 1885 and was admitted to the bar in 1887. He practiced law in New York City (1888-1947), and was active in municipal politics and affairs and served on several commissions, boards and associations.
Appendix: Select List of Correspondents Found in Series I
Abot, Edwin Hale 1834-1928
Abbott, John Stevens Cabot, 1805-1877
Abott, Nathan, 1854-1941
Adams, Andrew, 1736-1797
Adams, Charles Francis, 1835-1915
Adams, Charles Kendall, 1835-1902
Adams, Frederic, 1840-1923
Adams, George Burton, 1851-1925
Adams, Henry, 1838-1918
Adams, Herbert Baxter, 1850-1901
Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848
Adams, Sherman Wolcott, 1836-1889
Aiken, William Pope, 1866-1913
Aiken, William Appleton, 1833-1861
Aldrich, Fred Hampson, 1861-Â
Aldrich, Nelson Wilmarth, 1841-1915
Aldrich, Peleg Emory, 1813-1895
Aldrich, Thomas Bailey, 1836-1907
Allen, Heman, 1779-1852
Allen, James Albert, 1871-1929
Cinque (also known as Joseph Cinque? and Sengbe Pieh)
Allen, Walter, 1840-1907
Alling, John Wesley, 1841-1927
Allison, Andrew, 1894-Â
Allston, Washington, 1779-1843
Allibone, Samuel Austin, 1816-1889
Alter, Joseph Henry, 1820-1854
Ames, James Barr, 1846-1910
Anderson, Asher, 1846-1945
Anderson, Elbert Ellery, 1833-1903
Anderson, Joseph, 1836-1916
Anderson, Martin Brewer, 1815-1890
Anderson, Rufus, 1796-1880
Anderson, William Caldwell, 1852-1910
Andrew, Samuel Rogers, 1787-1858
Andrews, Catharine Augusta (Day), 1819-Â
Andrews, Charles Bartlett, 1834-1902
Andrews, Charles McLean, 1863-1943
Andrews, Elisha Benjamin, 1844-1917
Andrews, Ethan Allen, 1787-1858
Andrews, Horace, 1819-1901
Andrews, James DeWitt, 1856-1928
Andrews, John Whiting, 1811-1893
Andrews, William Given, 1835-1912
Andrews, William Turell, Â -1879
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916
Anketell, John, 1835-1905
Appleton, Nathan, 1843-1906
Arms, Hiram Phelps, 1789-1882
Arnot, Raymond Holbrook, 1873-1948
Ashman, George, 1804-1870
Atherton, George Washington, 1837-1906
Atwater, Isaac, 1818-1906
Atwater, Lyman Hotchkiss, 1813-1883
Atwater, Merritt Buckingham, 1823-1898
Atwater, William Lyman, 1820-Â
Auchmuty, Samuel, 1722-1777
Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
Austin, Samuel, 1760-1830
Averell, John Chester, 1849-Â
Averill, James George, 1818-1895
Babcock, James Fairchild, 1809-1874
Backus, Charles, 1749-1803
Backus, Joseph Willes, 1823-1901
Bacon, Arthur William, 1836-1907
Bacon, Asa, 1771-1857
Bacon, David Francis, 1813-1865
Bacon, Francis, 1819-1849
Bacon, Francis, 1831-1912
Bacon, Leonard Woolsey, 1830-1907
Bacon, Rebecca Taylor, 1826-1878
Bacon, Theodore, 1834-1900
Bacon, Thomas Rutherford, 1850-1913
Bagg, Lyman Hotchkiss, 1846-1911
Bailey, Mark, 1822-1904
Baird, John Gunn, 1826-1891
Baker, James Marion, 1861-1940
Baldwin, Anson, 1794-1860
Baldwin, Charles Candee, 1834-1895
Baldwin, Charles Francis, 1865-1941
Baldwin, Erastus, 1784-1841
Baldwin, Harvey, 1796-1863
Baldwin, Henry, 1780-1844
Baldwin, Henry, 1832-1905
Baldwin, James William, 1822-1889
Baldwin, John, 1717-1809
Baldwin, John Dennison, 1810-1883
Baldwin, Laommi, 1780-1838
Baldwin, Lloyd E., 1810-Â
Baldwin, Moses Harrison, 1811-1862
Baldwin, Oliver, 1747-1808
Baldwin, Roger Nash, 1884-Â
Baldwin, Theron, 1801-1891
Baldwin, Thomas, 1753-1825
Bancroft, George, 1800-1891
Barbour, Henry Stiles, 1822-1891
Barbour, John Strode, Jr. 1820-1892
Barbour, William Macleod, 1827-1899
Barday, Shepard, 1847-Â
Barker, John, 1754-1813
Barnard, Henry, 1811-1900
Barnard, Henry Clay, 1844-1929
Barnard, James Munson, 1819-1904
Barnes, Daniel, 1797-1873
Barnes, Jonathan, 1789-1861
Barrows, Charles Henry, 1853-1918
Barrows, Samuel June, 1845-1909
Bartlett, Elisha, 1804-1855
Bartlett, John Pomeroy, 1858-1948
Bates, Albert Carlos, 1865-Â
Bates, George Handy, 1845-1916
Bates, Isaac Chapman, 1779-1845
Battell, Joseph, 1774-1841
Bayard, Thomas Francis, 1828-1898
Bayne, Thomas Livingston, 1826-1891
Beach, Burrage, 1773-1844
Beach, George, 1788-1860
Beach, John Kimberley, 1855-1938
Beardsley, Morris Beach, 1849-1923
Beecher, George Buckingham, 1841-1925
Beers Elias, 1747-1832
Beers, George Emerson, 1865-1947
Beers, Henry Augustus, 1847-1926
Beers, Isaac, 1742-1813
Beers, Timothy Phelps, 1789-1858
Belcher, Nathan, 1813-1891
Belden, Hesekiah, 1778-1849
Bell, Clark, 1832-1918
Bellamy, Joseph Hart, 1788-1848
Benedict, Noble, 1735-1809
Benham, Henry Washington, 1813-1884
Benjamin, Reuben Moore, 1833-Â
Bennett, Joseph William, 1811-1883
Bennett, Milo Lyman, 1789-1868
Bent, Samuel Arthur, 1841-1912
Benton, Joseph Augustine, 1818-1892
Benton, Josiah Henry, 1843-1917
Bergh, Henry, 1811-1888
Bertram, James, 1872-1934
Betts, Frederic Henry, 1843-1905
Biddle, George Washington, 1818-1897
Bidwell, Barnabas, 1763-1833
Bidwell, Marshall Spring, 1799-1872
Bigelow, George Brooks, 1836-1901
Bigelow, John, 1817-1911
Bill, Arthur Gordon, 1856-1935
Bishop, Robert Roberts, 1834-1909
Bishop, William Darius, 1827-1904
Bissell, Champion, 1830-1899
Bissell, Clard, 1782-1857
Bissell, George Perkins, 1827-Â
Bissell, Josiah Hooker, 1845-1901
Black, Charles Frederic, 1834-1881
Black, Charles Thompson, 1826-1897
Black, Edward Foster, 1837-1862
Black, Henry Taylor, 1828-1922
Black, James Pierpont, 1839-1865
Blake, William Phipps, 1826-1910
Blanchard, Henry, 1833-1918
Blatchford, Charles Hammond, 1874-Â
Blatchford, Samuel, 1820-1893
Bloodgood, James, 1736-1799
Blumer, George, 1872-Â
Boardman, Daniel, 1757-1833
Boardman, William, 1805-1887
Boardman, William Whiting, 1794-1871
Bolles, Albert Sidney, 1846-1939
Bonney, Charles Carroll, 1831-1903
Booth, David Belden, 1824-1889
Booth, Henry, 1818-1898
Booth, Reuben, 1794-1848
Bosley, William Bradford, 1865-Â
Bowen, Clarence Winthrop, 1852-1935
Bowers, Edward Augustus, 1857-1924
Boyd, John, 1799-1881
Bradford, Gamaliel, 1831-1911
Bradish, Frank Eliot, Â -1914
Bradley, Charles Frederic, 1840-1896
Bradley, Charles Smith, 1819-1888
Bradley, Maria Hoadley, 1844-Â
Bradley, William Lockwook, 1837-1903
Brainard, Jeremiah Cates, 1759-1830
Brainerd, Cephas, Jr. 1831-1910
Bray, Frank Chapin, 1866-1949
Breed, Jesse, 1761-Â
Breed, Simeon, 1763-1822
Brenner, Victor David, 1871-1924
Brewer, David Josiah, 1837-1910
Brewer, Fisk Parsons, 1832-1890
Brewer, William Henry, 1828-1910
Brewster, James, 1788-1866
Brewster, John, 1816-Â
Brewster, John Frederick Flemmich, 1854-Â
Brewster, Lumen Dennison, 1832-1904
Bridgman, Howard Allen, 1860-1929
Bristol, Louis Henry, 1839-1910
Bristol, William, 1779-1836
Bristow, Benjamin Helm, 1832-1896
Brockett, Linus Pierpont, 1820-1893
Brockschmidt, Alfred John, 1860-1931
Bronson, Enos, 1774-1823
Bronson, Henry, 1804-1893
Brooks, Daniel, 1814-1861
Brooks, George Murray, 1857-1941
Brott, Grange Olney, 1867-1919
Brown, Edward Flint, 1839-1909
Brown, Henry Armitt, 1844-1878
Brown, Henry Billings, 1836-1913
Brown, Hubert Sanford, Â -1917
Bryce, James Bryce, Viscount, 1838-1922
Buchanan, James, Pres. U.S., 1791-1868
Buck, John Ranson, 1836-Â
Buckingham, William Alfred, 1804-1875
Buckland, Edward Grant, 1866-1953
Bulkeley, Eliphalet Adams, 1804-1872
Bulkeley, Morgan Gardner, 1837-1922
Bumpus, Hermon Carey, 1862-1943
Bunnell, Lyman Benham, 1832-1902
Burlingham, Charles C(ulp),
Burr, Alfred Edmund, 1815-1900
Burr, George Lincoln, 1857-Â
Burr, Sturges, 1760-1796
Burr, Thaddeus, 1735-1801
Burrall, Jonathan, 1753-1834
Burt, Andrew Sheridan, 1839-1915
Burton, Nathaniel Judson, 1824-1887
Bustamante y Sivrén, Antonio Sánebez de, 1865-Â
Butlan, William George, 1858-1935
Butler, John Simpkins, 1803-1890
Butler, Thomas Belden, 1806-1873
Butler, William Allen, 1825-1902
Byrington, Ezra Hoyt, 1828-1901
Cadman, Samuel Parkes, 1864-1936
Cady, Ernest, 1842-1908
Calderno de la Barca, Angel, 1790-1861
Calhoun, John Caldwell, 1782-1850
Calkins, Arthur B. Â -1867
Calkins, Wolcott, 1831-1924
Campbell, Henry French, Â -1904
Capen, Samuel Billings, 1842-1914
Carmalt, William Henry, 1836-1929
Carnegie, Andrew, 1835-1919
Carpenter, Elijah Whitney, Â -1881
Carpenter, Elisha, 1824-1897
Carpenter, John Frederic, 1870-1928
Carroll, Henry King, 1848-1931
Carter, James Coolodge, 1827-1905
Carter, Orrin Nelson, 1854-1928
Catlin, George, 1796-1872
Caulkins, Franic Manwaring, 1795-1869
Chadwick, Daniel, 1825-1884
Chamberlain, Daniel Henry, 1835-1907
Chamberlain, Leander Trowbridge, 1837-1913
Chamberlain, Levi, 1792-1848
Chamberlain, Myron Newton, 1836-1899
Chamberlain, Robert Linton, 1838-1888
Chamberlain, Valentine Burt, 1833-1893
Champion, Epaphroditus, 1786-1841
Champion, Henry, 1838-1867
Chandler, William Eaton, 1835-1917
Channing, Henry Trevett, 1760-1840
Chapin, Calvin, 1763-1851
Chapman, Charles, Richards, 1827-Â
Chauncey, Charles, 1777-1849
Chester, John, 1785-1829
Child, Cal in Goddard, 1834-1880
Child, Linus Mason, 1835-1898
Childs, William Vanlier, 1854-1910
Chilton, Harris Jones, Â -1917
Chittenden, Lucien Eugene, 1824-1900
Chittenden, Richard Handy, 1836-1911
Chittenden, Simeon Baldwin, 1845-1922
Choate, Joseph Hodges, 1832-1917
Church, Samuel, 1785-1854
Clap, Thomas, 1703-1767
Clark, Alonzo, 1807-1887
Clark, Charles Edward, 1889-Â
Clark, Charles Hopkins, 1848-1926
Clark, Edson Lyman, 1827-1913
Clark, Edward Lord, 1838-1910
Clark, Grange Lankin, 1849-Â
Clark, James Gardner, 1835-1905
Clark, John Emory, 1832-1921
Clark, William Barker, 1829-1905
Clarke, John Hopkins, 1789-1870
Clay, Henry, 1777-1852
Cleaveland, James Bradford, 1821-1889
Cleaveland, Livingston Warner, 1860-1929
Cleaveland, William Pitt, Jr., 1797-1841
Cleveland, Chauncey Fitch, 1799-1887
Cleveland, Stephen Grover, 1837-1908
Climons, Charles Frederic, 1871-1925
Clinton, DeWitt, 1767-1828
Cobbs, Thomas Harper, 1868-Â
Coe, Edward Benton, 1842-1914
Coe, Israel, 1794-Â
Coffey, Grange Henry, 1835-1885
Coffin, Owen Vincent, 1836-1921
Cogswell, Mason Fitch, 1761-1830
Coit, Alfred, 1863-1947
Coit, Charles, 1856-Â
Coit, Charles M., 1835-Â
Colby, James Fairbanks, 1850-1939
Collier, Peter, 1835-1896
Collins, John Chamberlain, 1850-1928
Colt, LeBaron Bradford, 1846-1924
Colton, George Hooker, 1818, 1847
Colton, Jabez, 1747-1819
Colton, James Hooper, 1832-1893
Convers, Ebenezer Buckingham, 1840-1905
Cook, Albert Stanburrough, 1853-1927
Cook, Joseph, 1838-1901
Cook, William, 1842-1886
Couch, Darius Nash, 1822-1897
Couse, Harvard Ambrose, 1871-Â
Cowles, James Lewis, 1843-1922
Crafts, Myron Harwood, 1816-1886
Crampton, Sir John Fienns Twisleton, 1817-1886
Crowell, John Franklin, 1857-1931
Crump, John Guy, Â -1894
Crump, William Cleaveland, 1816-1883
Currey, Samuel, 1806-1878
Curtis, Edward Lewis, Â -1911
Curtis, George Ticknor, 1812-1894
Curtis, Henry Holbrook, 1856-1920
Curtis, Howard Junior, 1857-1931
Cushing, Harry Alonso, 1870-1955
Dagrett, David, 1764-1851
Dagrett, Oliver Ellsworth, 1810-1880
Dallinger, Frederick William, 1871-Â
Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895
Dana, Richard Henry, 1815-1882
Dana, Samuel Whittelsey, 1760-1830
Daniels, Charles Herbert, 1847-1914
Davenport, Daniel, 1852-1931
Davenport, John Alfred, 1840-1890
Davenport, Reuben Briggs, Â -1932
Davies, Thomas Frederick, 1831-1985
Davis, Jefferson, 1808-1889
Davis, Josiah Gardner, 1815-1894
Day, George Edward, 1815-1905
Day, Jeremiah, 1773-1867
Day, Sherman, 1806-1884
De Forest, Andrew Woodward, 1817-1900
De Forest, David Curtis, 1774-1825
Denio, Hiram, 1799-1871
Denison, Albert, 1850-Â
Denison, Charles, 1778-1825
Depew, Chauncey Mitchell, 1834-1928
Dewell, James Dudley, 1870-1942
Dexter, Franklin Bowditch, 1842-1920
Dexter, Samuel, 1761-1816
Dickinson, Daniel Stevens, 1800-1866
Dickinson, Jacob McGavock, 1851-1928
Dickinson, James Taylor, 1806-1884
Dickinson, Marquis Fayette, 1840-Â
Dike, Samuel Warren, 1839-1913
Dillon, John Forrest, 1831-1914
Dilloway, Charles Knapp, Â -1889
Dilloway, George Wales, Â -1898
Dimock, Henry Farnam, 1842-1911
Dixon, James, 1814-1873
Dixwell, Epes Sargent, Â -1899
Dodge, William Earl, 1832-1903
Doolittle, Tilton Edwin, 1825-1896
Douglas, Benjamin, 1816-1894
Downes, William Elijah, 1824-1904
Drake, Joseph, 1737-1836
DuBois, Catherine Helene (Jay), 1815-1899
Duffield, Henry Martyn, 1842-1912
Dunbar, Charles Franklin, 1830-1900
Dunning, Albert Elijah, 1844-1923
Dutton, Henry, 1796-1869
Dutton, Samuel Train, 1849-1919
Dutton, Samuel William Southmayd, 1814-1866
Dwight, James McLaren Breed, 1825-1897
Dwight, Jane Wakeman (Skinner), 1832-1919
Dwight, Sereno Edward, 1786-1850
Dwight, Theodore, 1764-1846
Dwight, Theodore, William, 1822-1892
Dwight, Timothy, 1752-1817
Dwight, Timothy, 1778-1844
Dwight, Timothy, 1828-1916
Eaton, Amasa Mason, 1841-1914
Eaton, Dorman Bridgeman, 1823-1899
Eaton, Sherburne Balke, 1840-1914
Eaton, William Wallace, 1816-1898
Eaves, David William, 1831-1917
Edmunds, George Franklin, 1828-1917
Edwards, Alfred Lewis, 1836-1910
Edwards, Jonathan, 1745-1801
Edwards, Pierpont, 1750-1826
Eliot, Charles, William, 1834-1926
Elliot, Andrew, 1744-1805
Elliot, Andrew, 1744-1805
Elliot, Lewis Rossiter, 1819-1893
Elliott, Charles Wyllys, 1817-1883
Ellis, George Edward, 1814-1894
Ellsworth, Henry Leavitt, 1791-1868
Ely, Richard Theodore, 1854-1943
Elmore, Samuel Edward, 1833-1919
Emerson, Ralph, 1787-1863
Emery, Henry Crosby, 1872-1924
English, Henry Fowler, 1851-1947
English, James Edward, 1812-1890
Evarts, Jeremiah, 1781-1831
Evarts, William Maxwell, 1818-1901
Everett, Alexander Hill, 1790-1847
Everett, Edward, 1794-1865
Everett, William, 1839-1910
Fairbanks, Edward Taylor, 1836-1919
Fairchild, Robert, 1775-1835
Farnam, Henry Walcott, 1853-1933
Fay, George Austin, 1838-1916
Fellowes, Francis, 1803-1888
Fellowes, Frank Wayland, 1833-1900
Fenn, Augustus Hall, 1844-1897
Fenn, Bruce, 1857-1943
Fergus, Robert Collyer, 1868-1952
Ferry, Orris Sanford, 1823-1875
Fessenden, Samuel, 1847-1894
Fillmore, Millard, Pres. U.S., 1800-1874
Fine, John, 1784-1867
Fisher, George Park, 1827-1909
Fisher, Henry Johnson, 1873-Â
Fisher, Irving, 1867-1947
Fitch, Ebenezer, 1756-1833
Fitch, Lucius Wooster, 1820-1908
Fitzgerald, David Edward, 1874-1942
Flagg, Charles Noel, 1848-1916
Flagg, Henry Collins, 1792-1863
Flagg, William Joseph, 1818-1898
Follett, Martin Dewey, 1826-Â
Folsom, George, 1802-1869
Folsom, Joseph Robinson, Â -1911
Foot, John Alfred, 1803-1891
Foot, Samuel Augustus, 1780-1846
Fort, John Franklin, 1852-1928
Foss, Eugene Noble, 1858-Â
Foster, Alfred Dwight, 1800-1852
Foster, Alfred Dwight, 1852-1932
Foster, Dwight, 1828-1884
Foster, Eleazer, 1778-1819
Foster, John Watson, 1836-1917
Foster, LaFayette Sabine, 1806-1880
Foster, Reginald, 1863-1944
Foster, Roger Sherman Baldwin, 1857-1924
Foster, William Frederic, 1851-Â
Fowler, Lorenzo Miles, 1811-1896